Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Twin Fates=
=مصيران توأمان=
=Episode 18= (What Do You Like About Him?)
=الحلقة 18= (ما الذي يعجبك فيه؟)
No...
لا...
No!
لا!
No... No!
لا لا!
Your Majesty?
جلالتك؟
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
I bet you've just had
أراهن أنك قد حصلت للتو
a nightmare.
كابوس.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I will find and capture
سأجد وألتقط
that traitor who kidnapped you.
هذا الخائن الذي اختطفك.
I shall give him
سأعطيه
an ugly death.
موت قبيح.
No, please look into it, Your Majesty.
لا، من فضلك انظر في الأمر، جلالتك.
Chi Yu didn't kidnap me.
تشي يو لم يخطفني.
Bai Li of the Silver Fox Clan tried to kill us
حاول باي لي من عشيرة الثعلب الفضي قتلنا
with her plot.
مع مؤامرتها.
Whether it's Chi Yu
سواء كان تشي يو
or Bai Li,
أو باي لي،
I won't allow anyone to hurt you.
لن اسمح لأحد أن يؤذيك.
You belong to me.
أنت ملكي.
Your Majesty, what is this?
يا صاحب الجلالة، ما هذا؟
Ever since I first met you,
منذ أن التقيت بك لأول مرة،
I've fallen for you.
لقد وقعت في حبك.
Until now.
حتى الآن.
And I can't help myself.
ولا أستطيع مساعدة نفسي.
Since
منذ
you're not my cousin,
أنت لست ابن عمي
be my lady, then.
كن سيدتي إذن.
No, Your Majesty!
لا يا جلالتك!
No!
لا!
Your Majesty, go away!
جلالتك، اذهب بعيدا!
Let go!
اتركه!
I'm running out of patience.
لقد نفذ صبري.
I just want you.
انا فقط أريدك.
I want you now!
أريدك الآن!
Let go of me!
أتركني!
This trick
هذه الخدعة
seems familiar to me.
يبدو مألوفا بالنسبة لي.
Haven't you witnessed how powerful this trick is
ألم تشهد مدى قوة هذه الخدعة؟
when you first met me
عندما قابلتني لأول مرة
in the Silver Fox Palace?
في قصر الثعلب الفضي؟
I only saw Lord Silver Fox
لقد رأيت اللورد سيلفر فوكس فقط
and the princes lying in blood.
والأمراء ملطخين بالدماء.
That means
وهذا يعني
they died from...
لقد ماتوا من...
Did you really think
هل فكرت حقا
they died from killing one another
ماتوا بسبب قتل بعضهم البعض
after going berserk?
بعد أن أصبح مجنونا؟
(Idiot.)
(غبي.)
With them around,
مع وجودهم حولنا،
how could I inherit the throne?
كيف يمكنني أن أرث العرش؟
This is the Thousand-Soul Spell of Silver Fox Clan.
هذه هي تعويذة الألف روح لعشيرة الثعلب الفضي.
Whoever under this spell
من كان تحت هذا التعويذة
is short-tempered
سريع الغضب
and irrational.
وغير عقلاني.
So I get to kill without leaving a trace.
لذا أستطيع أن أقتل دون أن أترك أثراً.
(How cunning and cruel she is.)
(كم هي ماكرة وقاسية.)
Your power is admirable, Master.
قوتك رائعة يا سيدي.
Yet a game of power
ولكنها لعبة القوة
is always unpredictable, isn't it?
إنه أمر غير متوقع دائمًا، أليس كذلك؟
Are you giving me a heads-up
هل تعطيني تنبيها؟
or threatening me?
أو يهددني؟
I wouldn't dare to do so.
لا أجرؤ على فعل ذلك.
Know your place.
اعرف مكانك.
Remember.
يتذكر.
Your loyalty
ولائك
guarantees the authority I grant to you.
يضمن السلطة التي أمنحها لك.
Yes, I shall bear that in mind.
نعم، سأضع ذلك في الاعتبار.
Mu Lingxue.
مو لينج شيو.
You think hiding yourself in the palace
هل تعتقد أن إخفاء نفسك في القصر
will ensure your safety?
سوف تضمن سلامتك؟
(Loyalty?)
(وفاء؟)
(Once I've got the Xuanzhu Jade,)
(بمجرد حصولي على اليشم Xuanzhu)
(I'll show you what loyalty truly means.)
(سوف أريك ماذا يعني الولاء الحقيقي.)
(I'll prove that with your blood.)
(سوف أثبت ذلك بدمك.)
You do fancy me,
أنت معجب بي
right?
يمين؟
Well,
حسنًا،
you tried to get close to me time after time.
لقد حاولت التقرب مني مراراً وتكراراً.
You thought I hadn't figured that out, huh?
كنت تعتقد أنني لم أكتشف ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
Chi Yu...
تشي يو...
Your Majesty, please pardon us
جلالتك أرجوك أن تعفو عنا
for our tardiness!
لتأخرنا!
My beloved lady.
سيدتي الحبيبة.
You're up.
لقد استيقظت.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
I've been
لقد كنت
wondering about this.
أتساءل عن هذا.
What do you like
ماذا تريد
about him?
عنه؟
Is it his face,
هل هو وجهه؟
these eyes,
هذه العيون
or
أو
this mouth that bites people?
هذا الفم الذي يعض الناس؟
Stop it!
اوقفها!
Ji Yuchen, have you lost your mind?
جي يوتشن، هل فقدت عقلك؟
I have!
أملك!
In what way I'm less than him?
بأي طريقة أنا أقل منه؟
Why do you refuse to be my consort?
لماذا ترفض أن تكون زوجتي؟
Instead, you've been fooling around with him!
بدلا من ذلك، كنت تتلاعب معه!
Everything you've done with him,
كل ما فعلته معه،
I'll do them with you.
سأفعلها معك.
Mu Lingxue.
مو لينج شيو.
Just wait for me tonight.
فقط انتظرني الليلة.
I
أنا
will perform better than him.
سوف يؤدي بشكل أفضل منه.
In your dream!
في حلمك!
Fine.
بخير.
I'll get rid of him, then!
سأتخلص منه إذن!
No!
لا!
Are you threatening me
هل تهددني؟
with your life because of him?
مع حياتك بسببه؟
Yes.
نعم.
If you insist on killing him,
إذا أصريت على قتله،
kill me too.
اقتلني أيضا
Fine.
بخير.
I'll spare him.
سأوفره.
I want to marry you.
أريد الزواج منك.
I want us to be a loving couple.
أريد أن نكون زوجين محبين.
And I want him
وأنا أريده
to witness...
أن تشهد...
Guards.
حراس.
Prepare for my wedding
الاستعداد لحفل زفافي
with Noble Consort Mu.
مع الزوجة النبيلة مو.
Chi Yu...
تشي يو...
(No way, I need to do something to get him out of there.)
(لا يمكن، أنا بحاجة إلى القيام بشيء لإخراجه من هناك.)
Miss.
يفتقد.
Are you looking for someone?
هل تبحث عن شخص ما؟
How did you know that?
كيف عرفت ذلك؟
(Immortal Xi) Not only do I know
(الخالد شي) ليس فقط أنا أعرف
you're looking for someone,
(الخلود شي) كنت تبحث عن شخص ما،
but I'm also aware you're trying to save him.
ولكنني أدرك أيضًا أنك تحاول إنقاذه.
It's just that you don't know how.
إنك فقط لا تعرف كيف.
This concerns the secrets of the palace.
وهذا يتعلق بأسرار القصر.
Perhaps it has to do with the past.
ربما يتعلق الأمر بالماضي.
Please enlighten me, sir.
أرجو أن تنيرني يا سيدي.
The prince of Hong, Ji Yuchen,
أمير هونغ، جي يوشن،
has been frail and sickly since his childhood.
لقد كان ضعيفًا ومريضًا منذ طفولته.
Traitor Li Cang learned
الخائن لي كانغ تعلم
that the Silver Fox Clan possess a secret technique that could save his life.
أن عشيرة الثعلب الفضي تمتلك تقنية سرية يمكن أن تنقذ حياته.
Thus, he struck a deal with the King of Silver Fox Clan.
وبذلك، عقد صفقة مع ملك عشيرة الثعلب الفضي.
He'd remain loyal to the Silver Fox Clan
سيظل مخلصًا لعشيرة الثعلب الفضي
in exchange for the Prince's life.
في مقابل حياة الأمير.
And what saved the Prince's life
وما الذي أنقذ حياة الأمير؟
is none other than the primordial soul of Yanlie of the Scarlet Flame Clan.
ليست سوى الروح البدائية ليانلي من عشيرة اللهب القرمزي.
Master.
يتقن.
What should I do
ماذا علي أن أفعل
to save this Scarlet Flame Clan member who's lost his sanity
لإنقاذ هذا العضو من عشيرة اللهب القرمزي الذي فقد عقله
as well as golden feather?
وكذلك الريشة الذهبية؟
Yanlie is the only one who owns the golden feather
يانلي هو الوحيد الذي يملك الريشة الذهبية
in this world.
في هذا العالم.
And only Ji Yuchen could obtain the golden phoenix feather
وفقط جي يوتشن كان قادرًا على الحصول على ريشة العنقاء الذهبية
from Yanlie.
من يانلي.
Ji Yuchen?
جي يوشين؟
How do I get the feather from him?
كيف أحصل على الريشة منه؟
You know
أنت تعرف
what Ji Yuchen wants the most, don't you?
ما الذي يريده جي يوتشن أكثر من أي شيء آخر، أليس كذلك؟
It's you.
إنه أنت.
I've been a fortune-teller for years,
لقد كنت عرافة لسنوات،
and I've only figured out one thing.
ولقد توصلت إلى شيء واحد فقط.
Fate is all about
القدر هو كل شيء
making a choice.
اتخاذ خيار.
(There's only one way)
(هناك طريقة واحدة فقط)
(to get the golden phoenix feather)
(للحصول على ريشة الفينيق الذهبية)
(and help Chi Yu restore his sanity.)
(ومساعدة تشي يو على استعادة عقله.)
=Twin Fates= =End of Episode 18=
=مصيران توأمان= =نهاية الحلقة 18=
♪In a world of sorrows, every encounter is fleeting♪
في عالم من الأحزان، كل لقاء هو عابر؟
♪Life is short but slumber is long on Penglai Island♪
???الحياة قصيرة ولكن النوم طويل في جزيرة بنغلاي؟؟؟
♪In dreams, mountains and flowers are as beautiful as jade♪
???في الأحلام، الجبال والزهور جميلة مثل اليشم؟؟؟
♪All I ever wish for is an old friend's return♪
كل ما أتمناه هو عودة صديق قديم؟؟؟
♪Majestic as a soaring dragon, veiling the sun with drifting clouds♪
???مهيب مثل التنين المرتفع، يحجب الشمس بالغيوم المنجرفة؟؟؟
♪Graceful as a flying swan goose, breaking through snow and peril♪
???رشيقة مثل أوزة البجعة الطائرة، تخترق الثلوج والخطر ???
♪Twenty years forsaken, I lived the life of an outlaw♪
???بعد عشرين عامًا من الإهمال، عشت حياة خارجة عن القانون???
♪On the Ximo River, who was left behind?♪
???على نهر شيمو، من بقي خلفه ؟؟؟؟
♪Bit by bit, reality shatters my only hope♪
???شيئا فشيئا، الواقع يحطم أملي الوحيد؟؟؟
♪Layer by layer, cold blades roll up the light I once glimpsed in secret♪
???طبقة بعد طبقة، شفرات باردة تتدحرج نحو الضوء الذي لمحته ذات مرة سراً؟؟؟
♪Letters have long since yellowed♪
???لقد اصفرت الحروف منذ زمن طويل؟؟؟
♪Leaving only two lonely lines♪
???ترك خطين وحيدين فقط؟؟؟
♪Even the old yard is covered with frost♪
???حتى الفناء القديم مغطى بالصقيع؟؟؟
♪Pair after pair, swallows draw my envious gaze♪
???زوجًا بعد زوج، تجذب طيور السنونو نظرتي الحسود؟؟؟
♪Scene after scene, in dreams I cannot reach♪
???مشهد بعد مشهد، في الأحلام لا أستطيع الوصول إليه؟؟؟
♪While you rest beneath the earth♪
???بينما أنت تستريح تحت الأرض؟؟؟
♪My love lingers in this frosty world♪
"حبي لا يزال قائما في هذا العالم البارد"
♪How are you now?♪
????كيف حالك الآن ؟؟؟؟